{
    "id": "f115c66e91d34560aac2f640a4ddba86",
    "title": "Do and make – grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "860542a3c5e54fa29bcb069552e8eef6",
            "title": "Do And Make Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He made me …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "to wait"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………… the whole story.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made to repeat",
                        "was made repeating",
                        "was made to repeat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t speak French well, but I can ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make myself understand",
                        "make me understand",
                        "make myself understood"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had to shout to ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make me heard",
                        "make myself heard",
                        "make myself hear"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Paper is made …………………. wood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "out of",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is time to ………………… the accounts.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "make",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He likes ……………….. nothing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "doing",
                        "making"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is old enough to ……………. her own bed now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She lost her money. I wasn’t surprised that she …………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you ever made wine ………………. blackberries?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "with",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}